(Sheldon:)and I assumed
my career would continue
(Sheldon:)on that upward trajectory.
(Sheldon:)Now here I am in my 30s,
(Sheldon:)I'm back at square one.
(Sheldon:)And, frankly, it's frightening.
(Raj:)Sheldon, you know
what I think of when I'm scared?
Voyager.
Voyager the space probe
or Voyager
the Star Trek TV show?
(Sheldon:)The space probe.
(Penny:)Good.
Because I am too hot and tired
(Sheldon:)to go on about how much
I hate Voyager the TV show.
(Raj:)By the time
I was born,
Voyager 1's mission
was supposed to be over.
(Raj:)It had seen
(Raj:)Jupiter and Saturn
and all their moons,
(Raj:)but it kept going.
(Raj:)When I left India for America,
(Raj:)I was never more scared
in my life.
(Raj:)I had no idea
what lay ahead.
(Raj:)Whenever I feel that way,
I think about how...
Voyager is still out there